    全新版第二版综合B3U8-C

    Part I    Listening Comprehension  ( 15 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear ten statements. Numbers 1 to 6 are based on Text A while the rest are based on Text B. Each statement will be read ONLY ONCE. Listen carefully and decide whether each statement is true or false.


    1.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: It was absolutely horrifying for the author when his mother lost her eyesight and most of her ability to walk.

    正确答案： A
    2.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: In 2004 and 2005 it was known that Hwang Woo-Suk succeeded in creating human embryonic stem cells by cloning.

    正确答案： B
    3.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: Human reproductive cloning is just simply wrong ethically from a medical standpoint and a scientific standpoint.

    正确答案： A
    4.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: The majority of reproductive clones in other species are actually normal, without miscarriage rates, stillbirth rates, fetal anomalies, death soon after birth, et cetera.

    正确答案： B
    5.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: Therapeutic cloning does involve risk to human life, providing tremendous potential for the relief of suffering in real human beings.

    正确答案： B
    6.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: There’s really no effective way for an individual scientist to stop someone else from using the knowledge for something they shouldn’t.

    正确答案： A
    7.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: Dolly was created in the laboratory from a single cell of “parent”.

    正确答案： A
    8.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: California enacted a ban on human cloning, and the President's National Bioethics Advisory Commission recommended making the ban nationwide.

    正确答案： A
    9.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: The author subscribes to the view that the Constitution necessarily guarantees every individual the right to reproduce through any possible means.

    正确答案： B
    10.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: To ban cloning may, in the end, lend support to strikingly similar objections to surrogate motherhood.

    正确答案： A


    Section B 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear a passage three times. When the passage is read for the first time, you should listen carefully for its general idea. When the passage is read for the second time, you are required to fill in the blanks with the exact words you have just heard. Finally, when the passage is read for the third time, you should check what you have written.


            Human cloning is no longer a dream in the wake of the birth of the first cloned sheep, Dolly, in 1996. Since that moment, not only the scientists in the field of (11)_________________ , but also the people over the whole world, have focused their (12)_________________ on whether humanity should be cloned or not. Undoubtedly, human cloning has already become the most (13)_________________ issue for a period. But seemingly, people haven’t got tired of the endless debates on this topic. The most (14)_________________ consideration during the debate is if human cloning can bring about good more than harm to society or not.
            Apparently, one of the well-known (15)_________________ brought about by human cloning is medical advance. Once a cell is (16)_________________ using the genetic materials derived from its host, the cell can act as a primary cell (17)_________________ of dividing and differentiating into specialized cells such as liver cells as well as nerve cells, and then develop into some kinds of vital organs. This sounds incredible, in particular to those who long for transplants to prolong their lives. Apart from this, during the process of nurturing the cloned embryo, scientists can extend their scope of knowledge about (18)_________________ and mechanism of certain fatal and incurable diseases like Parkinson’s disease, cancer and AIDs. On the basis of such discoveries, scientists are able to explore more ways to (19)_________________ . Furthermore, according to many scientists’ statements, the ageing process could be hindered if human cloning proceeded successfully. This means the impractical dream of extending the average lifespan of humanity to 120 years could (20)_________________ . As long as all nations strictly control the use of human cloning, human cloning will do more good than harm.

    Script:         Human cloning is no longer a dream in the wake of the birth of the first cloned sheep, Dolly, in 1996. Since that moment, not only the scientists in the field of biotechnology, but also the people over the whole world, have focused their attentions on whether humanity should be cloned or not. Undoubtedly, human cloning has already become the most controversial issue for a period. But seemingly, people haven’t got tired of the endless debates on this topic. The most crucial consideration during the debate is if human cloning can bring about good more than harm to society or not.
            Apparently, one of the well-known benefits brought about by human cloning is medical advance. Once a cell is duplicated using the genetic materials derived from its host, the cell can act as a primary cell capable of dividing and differentiating into specialized cells such as liver cells as well as nerve cells, and then develop into some kinds of vital organs. This sounds incredible, in particular to those who long for transplants to prolong their lives. Apart from this, during the process of nurturing the cloned embryo, scientists can extend their scope of knowledge about the mysterious causes and mechanism of certain fatal and incurable diseases like Parkinson’s disease, cancer and AIDs. On the basis of such discoveries, scientists are able to explore more ways to combat the diseases. Furthermore, according to many scientists’ statements, the ageing process could be hindered if human cloning proceeded successfully. This means the impractical dream of extending the average lifespan of humanity to 120 years could ultimately become reality. As long as all nations strictly control the use of human cloning, human cloning will do more good than harm.

    正确答案： biotechnology

    正确答案： attentions

    正确答案： controversial

    正确答案： crucial

    正确答案： benefits

    正确答案： duplicated

    正确答案： capable

    正确答案： the mysterious causes

    正确答案： combat the diseases

    正确答案： ultimately become reality



    Part II    Reading Comprehension  ( 25 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, there is a passage with several blanks. You are required to select one word for each blank from a list of choices given in a word bank following the passage. Read the passage through carefully before making your choices. Each choice in the bank is identified by a letter. You may not use any of the words in the bank more than once.


            I always thought that when our research was successful that I would just be pleased that we had   21    this when others had not. In reality, it is   22    — when you look through the microscope, you see what you may have looked like a long time ago, at least in part.
            When I looked down and saw that cloned   23    , it brought tears to my eyes. I had done this for my mother, and I realized,   24    she only been able to live a few years longer, maybe we could have used this technology to help her. It was   25    to see that potential, which she never had a chance to experience.
            There’s a big   26    out there that we decided to destroy these embryos for some reason. There was so much   27    about this process because of the scientific   28    from the past that it was critical that there be no doubt that they were clones.
            In the process of analysis, the embryos were destroyed by   29    . In other words, to get the   30    material from inside the cells to analyze it, you have to destroy the cell.

    A) if	B) genetically	C) fraud	D) transparent
    E) emotion	F) transcendent	G) blastocyst	H) skepticism
    I) emotional	J) skeptical	K) misconception	L) genetic
    M) had	N) necessity	O) accomplished	

    21.	______________________

    正确答案： O

    22.	______________________

    正确答案： F

    23.	______________________

    正确答案： G

    24.	______________________

    正确答案： M

    25.	______________________

    正确答案： I

    26.	______________________

    正确答案： K

    27.	______________________

    正确答案： H

    28.	______________________

    正确答案： C

    29.	______________________

    正确答案： N

    30.	______________________

    正确答案： L


    Section B 

    Directions: There are several passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice.


    Passage One
    Questions 31 to 35 are based on the following passage.



            Depending on whom you ask, the experiment announced at a Texas medical conference last week was a potential breakthrough for infertile women, a tragic failure or a dangerous step closer to the nightmare scenario of human cloning.
            Infertility was clearly the motivation when Chinese doctors used a new technique to help one of their countrywomen get pregnant. Using a technique developed by Dr. James Grifo at New York University, Dr. Zhuang Guanglun of Sun Yat-sen University in Guangzhou took the patient’s fertilized egg, scooped out the chromosome-bearing nuclear material and put it in a donated egg whose nucleus had been removed. In this more benign environment, development proceeded normally, and the woman became pregnant with triplets who carried a mix of her DNA and her husband’s — pretty much like any normal baby.
            What has made some doctors and ethicists upset is that this so-called nuclear-transfer technique has also been used to produce clones, starting with Dolly the sheep. The only significant difference is that with cloning, the inserted nucleus comes from a single, usually adult, cell, and the resulting offspring is genetically identical to the parent. Doing that with humans is ethically repugnant to many. Besides, for reasons that aren’t yet well understood, cloned animals often abort spontaneously or are born with defects; Dolly died very young, though she had seemed healthy. And because the Chinese woman’s twins were born prematurely and died, critics have suggested that cloning and nuclear transfer are equally risky for humans.
            Not likely, says Grifo. “The obstetric outcome was a disaster,” he admits, “but the embryos were chromosomally normal. We have no evidence that it had anything to do with the procedure.” Even so, concern over potential risks is why the Food and Drug Administration created a stringent approval process for such research in 2001 — a process that Grifo found so onerous that he stopped working on the technique and gave it to the researchers in China, where it was subsequently banned.
            The bottom line, say critics, is that perfecting a technique that could be used for human cloning, even if it were developed for another purpose, is just a bad idea — an assertion Zhuang rejects. “I agree that it makes sense to control these experiments,” he says. “But we’ve developed an effective technology to help people. We understand how to do it. We need it.”

    31.
    	
    What is implied in the first paragraph?
    A) Some people regard it as a tragic failure.  
    B) The new experiment means a breakthrough for some people.  
    C) People have different reactions to the new experiment.  
    D) The new experiment means a step further to the dangerous human cloning.  

    正确答案： C
    32.
    	
    The author uses the case of Dolly and the Chinese pregnant woman to show that _________.
    A) both nuclear-transfer and cloning are dangerous for humans and animals  
    B) both of them benefit from the new technique  
    C) both of them are the examples of technical failure  
    D) both of them are the fruits of the new technology  

    正确答案： A
    33.
    	
    Zhuang’s attitude toward the critics’ conclusion is one of __________.
    A) reserved consent  
    B) strong disapproval  
    C) slight contempt  
    D) enthusiastic support  

    正确答案： B
    34.
    	
    The only difference existing between nuclear-transfer and cloning technique is ________.
    A) whether it is used for research or for helping the infertile  
    B) whether the offspring looks like the parent  
    C) whether it is used in animals or human beings  
    D) whether the inserted nucleus comes from a single and usually adult cell  

    正确答案： D
    35.
    	
    The text intends to express the idea that _________.
    A) research of cloning has potential risks  
    B) the research of cloning should be stopped totally  
    C) ethics and research of cloning are in contradiction  
    D) researchers should have the right to continue the study of cloning  

    正确答案： C

    Passage Two
    Questions 36 to 40 are based on the following passage.



            If a couple are infertile and wish they were not, that is sad. But there are treatments intended to deal with this sadness — known collectively as assisted reproductive technologies, or ARTs, which should be paid for out of public funds. Such funds are scarce, and infertility is not a life-threatening condition.
            However, two papers presented to the “State of the ART” conference held earlier this month in Lyon argue that in Europe, at least, there may be a public interest in promoting ARTs after all. The low fertility rate in many of that continent’s more developed countries means their populations are ageing and shrinking. If governments want to change this, ARTs — most significantly in-vitro fertilization (IVF) — could offer at least part of a way to do so.
            Tina Jensen of the University of Southern Denmark has just finished a study of more than 700,000 Danish women. She found that young women in Denmark have a significantly lower natural conception rate than in past decades. Whatever the cause, she also found that the effect has been almost completely compensated for by an increasing use of ARTs. Denmark’s native population is more or less stable, but some 3.9% of babies born there in 2003 were the result of IVF. The comparable figure for another northern European country, Britain, was 1.5%.
            Without IVF, then, the number of Danes would be shrinking fast. That may not have something to do with the fact that in Denmark the taxpayer will cover up to six cycles of IVF treatment. In Britain, by contrast, couples are supposed to be entitled to three cycles. In practice, many of the local trusts that dish the money out do not pay for any cycles at all. Jonathan Grant, the head of the Cambridge branch of the Rand Corporation, believes this is shortsighted.
            The cost of offering six cycles to couples would be an extra £250m-430m a year. That is not trivial, but Dr Grant reckons it is cheaper than other ways of boosting the birth rate.
            There are, of course, some disadvantages to promoting IVF. In particular, women who use it tend to be older than those who conceive naturally, and that can lead to congenital problems in their children. But if the countries of Europe do wish to keep their populations up, making IVF more widely available might be a good way of doing so.

    36.
    	
    According to the text, the public’s opinion on the infertility treatments is that _____.
    A) the treatments should be paid for out of public funds  
    B) the treatments are not so compulsory as they consume the limited public funds  
    C) the treatments are not necessarily only paid for out of public funds  
    D) the public is not obliged to pay for such treatments of no urgent nature  

    正确答案： B
    37.
    	
    According to the study conducted by Tina Jensen, which one of the following statements is true?
    A) ARTs have reversed the tendency of population decreasing in Denmark.  
    B) Danes’s problem of low natural conception has been completely counterbalanced by the widely use of ARTs.  
    C) The population of Denmark is not decreasing after the adoption of ARTs.  
    D) IVF has played an essential role in Denmark in terms of keeping up the number of population.  

    正确答案： D
    38.
    	
    From the paper of Dr Grant, it can be inferred that ______.
    A) the cost of offering six cycles of IVF to couples is not high at all  
    B) IVF treatment is an economical way of solving population shrinking  
    C) Britain does not promote adopting IVF to boost the birth rate  
    D) encouraging women to bear more babies by bonus is not so efficient to solve the problem of population shrinking  

    正确答案： B
    39.
    	
    The word “congenital” in the last paragraph most probably means _____.
    A) innate  
    B) instinctive  
    C) cerebral  
    D) acquired  

    正确答案： A
    40.
    	
    According to the passage, the author’s attitude towards promoting in-vitro fertilization can be said to be _____.
    A) supportive  
    B) opposing  
    C) ambiguous  
    D) objective  

    正确答案： A



    Part III    Vocabulary and Structure  ( 10 minutes ) 



    Directions: There are a number of incomplete sentences in this part. For each sentence there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). Choose the ONE that best completes the sentence.


    41.
    	
    It is _________ to think that students graduate without a thorough understanding of the subject matter.
    A) horrifying  
    B) horrified  
    C) horrible  
    D) hopeless  

    正确答案： A
    42.
    	
    From the __________ of this work, this is an extreme point of view which is inapplicable.
    A) view  
    B) speech  
    C) standpoint  
    D) scene  

    正确答案： C
    43.
    	
    The police managed to ________ him from jumping off the building.
    A) persuade  
    B) persuasion  
    C) dissuasion  
    D) dissuade  

    正确答案： D
    44.
    	
    With the clear perception of my ___________ , there fell upon me a blackness of despair.
    A) flight  
    B) delight  
    C) plight  
    D) light  

    正确答案： C
    45.
    	
    He can not find it in himself to ________ a mother who stole bread for a hungry child.
    A) flatter  
    B) sue  
    C) judge  
    D) condemn  

    正确答案： D
    46.
    	
    There is no definite age at which _________ functions cease abruptly during life in man.
    A) production  
    B) productive  
    C) reproduction  
    D) reproductive  

    正确答案： D
    47.
    	
    Most people want tougher environmental ________ but large corporations continue to oppose it.
    A) legislate  
    B) publication  
    C) legislation  
    D) routine  

    正确答案： C
    48.
    	
    More women ________ as candidates than ever before.
    A) come to  
    B) come in  
    C) come forward  
    D) come upon  

    正确答案： C
    49.
    	
    Professor Wang looks very kind but, ________, he is very hard on us.
    A) in real  
    B) essentially  
    C) in reality  
    D) in essence  

    正确答案： C
    50.
    	
    To be _________, the argument in your graduation thesis is logical.
    A) specific  
    B) particular  
    C) special  
    D) especial  

    正确答案： A
    51.
    	
    He said that sex discrimination laws had not really succeeded in changing _____ views about the roles of men and women in society.
    A) specific  
    B) traditional  
    C) ancient  
    D) artificial  

    正确答案： B
    52.
    	
    After 18 hours of _____ and weeks of intensive care, Jerry was released from the hospital with fragments of the bullets still in his body.
    A) mixture  
    B) surgery  
    C) complaining  
    D) palsy  

    正确答案： B
    53.
    	
    I understand why I imagined being robbed by a man: they're physically more dominating and I've never _____ anyone being robbed by a female.
    A) heard of  
    B) been bound to  
    C) headed for  
    D) had second thoughts on  

    正确答案： A
    54.
    	
    We arrived at the ______ room at 2:30 and our baby was born at 3:30.
    A) rendezvous  
    B) delivery  
    C) testimony  
    D) appreciation  

    正确答案： B
    55.
    	
    Fleischer would not say whether Bush asked Sharon to hold his fire if attacked by Iraq ______ a U.S.-led war.
    A) amid  
    B) into  
    C) between  
    D) rear  

    正确答案： A
    56.
    	
    We collected hundreds of _____ in support of not allowing cars into the city centre.
    A) signatures  
    B) awareness  
    C) stationery  
    D) statements  

    正确答案： A
    57.
    	
    American surgeon performed the first artificial heart ________ on a human being in 1969.
    A) transparent  
    B) transplant  
    C) implant  
    D) transmission  

    正确答案： B
    58.
    	
    What's the ________ for opening a savings account?
    A) procedure  
    B) series  
    C) method  
    D) measure  

    正确答案： A
    59.
    	
    The police managed to ________ him from jumping off the building.
    A) persuade  
    B) persuasion  
    C) dissuasion  
    D) dissuade  

    正确答案： D
    60.
    	
    According to Bernoulli's Principle, the higher the speed of a fluid gas, ________ the pressure.
    A) it will be lower  
    B) lower than the  
    C) the lower  
    D) lower it is  

    正确答案： C



    Part IV    Translation  ( 10 minutes ) 



    Directions: Complete the sentences by translating into English the Chinese given in brackets.


    61. 	The boy was so much frightened ____________________ (他紧紧抓住母亲的手臂不肯松手).

    正确答案： that he caught tight his mother's arm and would not let loose
    62. 	____________________ (无论何时你想要表达你的意见), please look before leap.

    正确答案： Whenever you feel like expressing you opinion
    63. 	I think ____________________ (这一主题本应吸引哲学家们更多的注意力) than it has attracted attention from us.

    正确答案： this topic should have attracted far more attention from philosophers
    64. 	No one can say that ____________________ (他能抵御周围环境对他的影响) unless he is living in a vacuum.

    正确答案： he is immune to the influence around him
    65. 	That day ____________________ (他有许多工作要做，忙得疲于奔命) and didn't have the least rest.

    正确答案： he was run off his feet with jobs to do


