    全新版第二版综合B3U8-B

    Part I    Listening Comprehension  ( 15 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear ten statements. Numbers 1 to 6 are based on Text A while the rest are based on Text B. Each statement will be read ONLY ONCE. Listen carefully and decide whether each statement is true or false.


    1.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: It was absolutely horrifying for the author when his mother lost her eyesight and most of her ability to walk.

    正确答案： A
    2.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: In 2004 and 2005 it was known that Hwang Woo-Suk succeeded in creating human embryonic stem cells by cloning.

    正确答案： B
    3.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: Human reproductive cloning is just simply wrong ethically from a medical standpoint and a scientific standpoint.

    正确答案： A
    4.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: The majority of reproductive clones in other species are actually normal, without miscarriage rates, stillbirth rates, fetal anomalies, death soon after birth, et cetera.

    正确答案： B
    5.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: Therapeutic cloning does involve risk to human life, providing tremendous potential for the relief of suffering in real human beings.

    正确答案： B
    6.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: There’s really no effective way for an individual scientist to stop someone else from using the knowledge for something they shouldn’t.

    正确答案： A
    7.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: Dolly was created in the laboratory from a single cell of “parent”.

    正确答案： A
    8.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: California enacted a ban on human cloning, and the President's National Bioethics Advisory Commission recommended making the ban nationwide.

    正确答案： A
    9.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: The author subscribes to the view that the Constitution necessarily guarantees every individual the right to reproduce through any possible means.

    正确答案： B
    10.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: To ban cloning may, in the end, lend support to strikingly similar objections to surrogate motherhood.

    正确答案： A


    Section B 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear a passage three times. When the passage is read for the first time, you should listen carefully for its general idea. When the passage is read for the second time, you are required to fill in the blanks with the exact words you have just heard. Finally, when the passage is read for the third time, you should check what you have written.


            Human cloning is no longer a dream in the wake of the birth of the first cloned sheep, Dolly, in 1996. Since that moment, not only the scientists in the field of (11)_________________ , but also the people over the whole world, have focused their (12)_________________ on whether humanity should be cloned or not. Undoubtedly, human cloning has already become the most (13)_________________ issue for a period. But seemingly, people haven’t got tired of the endless debates on this topic. The most (14)_________________ consideration during the debate is if human cloning can bring about good more than harm to society or not.
            Apparently, one of the well-known (15)_________________ brought about by human cloning is medical advance. Once a cell is (16)_________________ using the genetic materials derived from its host, the cell can act as a primary cell (17)_________________ of dividing and differentiating into specialized cells such as liver cells as well as nerve cells, and then develop into some kinds of vital organs. This sounds incredible, in particular to those who long for transplants to prolong their lives. Apart from this, during the process of nurturing the cloned embryo, scientists can extend their scope of knowledge about (18)_________________ and mechanism of certain fatal and incurable diseases like Parkinson’s disease, cancer and AIDs. On the basis of such discoveries, scientists are able to explore more ways to (19)_________________ . Furthermore, according to many scientists’ statements, the ageing process could be hindered if human cloning proceeded successfully. This means the impractical dream of extending the average lifespan of humanity to 120 years could (20)_________________ . As long as all nations strictly control the use of human cloning, human cloning will do more good than harm.

    Script:         Human cloning is no longer a dream in the wake of the birth of the first cloned sheep, Dolly, in 1996. Since that moment, not only the scientists in the field of biotechnology, but also the people over the whole world, have focused their attentions on whether humanity should be cloned or not. Undoubtedly, human cloning has already become the most controversial issue for a period. But seemingly, people haven’t got tired of the endless debates on this topic. The most crucial consideration during the debate is if human cloning can bring about good more than harm to society or not.
            Apparently, one of the well-known benefits brought about by human cloning is medical advance. Once a cell is duplicated using the genetic materials derived from its host, the cell can act as a primary cell capable of dividing and differentiating into specialized cells such as liver cells as well as nerve cells, and then develop into some kinds of vital organs. This sounds incredible, in particular to those who long for transplants to prolong their lives. Apart from this, during the process of nurturing the cloned embryo, scientists can extend their scope of knowledge about the mysterious causes and mechanism of certain fatal and incurable diseases like Parkinson’s disease, cancer and AIDs. On the basis of such discoveries, scientists are able to explore more ways to combat the diseases. Furthermore, according to many scientists’ statements, the ageing process could be hindered if human cloning proceeded successfully. This means the impractical dream of extending the average lifespan of humanity to 120 years could ultimately become reality. As long as all nations strictly control the use of human cloning, human cloning will do more good than harm.

    正确答案： biotechnology

    正确答案： attentions

    正确答案： controversial

    正确答案： crucial

    正确答案： benefits

    正确答案： duplicated

    正确答案： capable

    正确答案： the mysterious causes

    正确答案： combat the diseases

    正确答案： ultimately become reality



    Part II    Reading Comprehension  ( 25 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, there is a passage with several blanks. You are required to select one word for each blank from a list of choices given in a word bank following the passage. Read the passage through carefully before making your choices. Each choice in the bank is identified by a letter. You may not use any of the words in the bank more than once.


            Human reproductive cloning is just simply wrong   21    from a medical standpoint and a scientific standpoint, even   22    any religious issues associated with it. The reason is that the majority of reproductive clones in other species are actually   23    , with very high   24    rates, very high stillbirth rates, fetal anomalies, death soon after birth, et cetera.
            It would just be absolutely wrong to take a human being and   25    what may well involve significant suffering for really no good end. Even though people could take the techniques that we’ve developed and   26    to do it, we hope that they would not.
            On the other hand,   27    cloning does not involve any type of risk to human life and actually provides   28    potential for the relief of suffering in real human beings who are going through some awful things.
            I’m a pure scientist in some ways, and I know that many different studies or findings could be used for   29    . Our job as scientists is to make the most of this technology and make it   30    to the greatest number of other scientists who can help us do good things with it.

    A) devil	B) tremendous	C) therapeutic	D) abnormal
    E) miscarriage	F) attempt	G) put them through	H) ethically
    I) ignoring	J) therapy	K) tempt	L) evil
    M) available	N) ethnics	O) get them through	

    21.	______________________

    正确答案： H

    22.	______________________

    正确答案： I

    23.	______________________

    正确答案： D

    24.	______________________

    正确答案： E

    25.	______________________

    正确答案： G

    26.	______________________

    正确答案： F

    27.	______________________

    正确答案： C

    28.	______________________

    正确答案： B

    29.	______________________

    正确答案： L

    30.	______________________

    正确答案： M


    Section B 

    Directions: There are several passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice.


    Passage One
    Questions 31 to 35 are based on the following passage.



            If a couple are infertile and wish they were not, that is sad. But there are treatments intended to deal with this sadness — known collectively as assisted reproductive technologies, or ARTs, which should be paid for out of public funds. Such funds are scarce, and infertility is not a life-threatening condition.
            However, two papers presented to the “State of the ART” conference held earlier this month in Lyon argue that in Europe, at least, there may be a public interest in promoting ARTs after all. The low fertility rate in many of that continent’s more developed countries means their populations are ageing and shrinking. If governments want to change this, ARTs — most significantly in-vitro fertilization (IVF) — could offer at least part of a way to do so.
            Tina Jensen of the University of Southern Denmark has just finished a study of more than 700,000 Danish women. She found that young women in Denmark have a significantly lower natural conception rate than in past decades. Whatever the cause, she also found that the effect has been almost completely compensated for by an increasing use of ARTs. Denmark’s native population is more or less stable, but some 3.9% of babies born there in 2003 were the result of IVF. The comparable figure for another northern European country, Britain, was 1.5%.
            Without IVF, then, the number of Danes would be shrinking fast. That may not have something to do with the fact that in Denmark the taxpayer will cover up to six cycles of IVF treatment. In Britain, by contrast, couples are supposed to be entitled to three cycles. In practice, many of the local trusts that dish the money out do not pay for any cycles at all. Jonathan Grant, the head of the Cambridge branch of the Rand Corporation, believes this is shortsighted.
            The cost of offering six cycles to couples would be an extra £250m-430m a year. That is not trivial, but Dr Grant reckons it is cheaper than other ways of boosting the birth rate.
            There are, of course, some disadvantages to promoting IVF. In particular, women who use it tend to be older than those who conceive naturally, and that can lead to congenital problems in their children. But if the countries of Europe do wish to keep their populations up, making IVF more widely available might be a good way of doing so.

    31.
    	
    According to the text, the public’s opinion on the infertility treatments is that _____.
    A) the treatments should be paid for out of public funds  
    B) the treatments are not so compulsory as they consume the limited public funds  
    C) the treatments are not necessarily only paid for out of public funds  
    D) the public is not obliged to pay for such treatments of no urgent nature  

    正确答案： B
    32.
    	
    According to the study conducted by Tina Jensen, which one of the following statements is true?
    A) ARTs have reversed the tendency of population decreasing in Denmark.  
    B) Danes’s problem of low natural conception has been completely counterbalanced by the widely use of ARTs.  
    C) The population of Denmark is not decreasing after the adoption of ARTs.  
    D) IVF has played an essential role in Denmark in terms of keeping up the number of population.  

    正确答案： D
    33.
    	
    From the paper of Dr Grant, it can be inferred that ______.
    A) the cost of offering six cycles of IVF to couples is not high at all  
    B) IVF treatment is an economical way of solving population shrinking  
    C) Britain does not promote adopting IVF to boost the birth rate  
    D) encouraging women to bear more babies by bonus is not so efficient to solve the problem of population shrinking  

    正确答案： B
    34.
    	
    The word “congenital” in the last paragraph most probably means _____.
    A) innate  
    B) instinctive  
    C) cerebral  
    D) acquired  

    正确答案： A
    35.
    	
    According to the passage, the author’s attitude towards promoting in-vitro fertilization can be said to be _____.
    A) supportive  
    B) opposing  
    C) ambiguous  
    D) objective  

    正确答案： A

    Passage Two
    Questions 36 to 40 are based on the following passage.

            The oldest and simplest method, then of describing differences in personality was to classify people according to types, and such a system is called a Typology.
            A famous example of this method was set forth in Greece about the year 400 BC. A physician named Hippocrates theorized that there were four fluids, or humors, in the body. Corresponding to each humor, he believed, there existed a definite type of personality.
            The four humors were blood, yellow bile, black bile, and phlegm. A person in whom all four humors were in perfect balance had a harmonious personality. If a person had too much blood, he was called sanguine (血红色), or cheerful and optimistic. Someone with too much yellow bile was choleric, or irritable and easily angered. Too much black bile made a person melancholy, or depressed and pessimistic. An oversupply of phlegm caused a human being to be phlegmatic, or slow and unfeeling. Scientists have long since discarded Hippocrates' fluid theory. But the names of the humors, corresponding to these temperaments, have survived and are still useful, to some extent, in describing personality.
            Other features of people, such as their faces and physics, have also been used to classify personality. Today, however, personality theories and classifications may also include factors such as heredity (遗传特征), the environment, intelligence, and emotional needs. Psychology, biology, and sociology are involved in these theories. Because of the complexity of human personality, present day theories are often very different from one another. Psychologists vary in their ideas about what is most important in determining personality.



    36.
    	
    According to Hippocrates' fluid theory, a man with too much phlegm will be ________.
    A) optimistic  
    B) easily angered  
    C) unexcitable  
    D) pessimistic  

    正确答案： C
    37.
    	
    The main idea of this passage is about ______.
    A) the complicated factors in determining one's personality  
    B) Hippocrates' fluid theory and its development  
    C) the past and today of personality classifications and theories  
    D) different personalities and their details  

    正确答案： C
    38.
    	
    At present, psychologists ___________.
    A) have common opinion about personality theories and classifications  
    B) use biology, archaeology and sociology to study personality theories  
    C) have abandoned Hippocrates' fluid theory entirely  
    D) all agree that human beings are characterized with complex personalities  

    正确答案： D
    39.
    	
    The third paragraph mainly talks about _________.
    A) Hippocrates' fluid theory  
    B) scientists' points of view on Hippocrates' fluid theory  
    C) Hippocrates' fluid theory and its fate  
    D) defects in Hippocrates' fluid theory  

    正确答案： C
    40.
    	
    According to this passage, the factors which are still NOT used to classify personality are ______.
    A) one's born features and needs of love and success  
    B) one's height and weight  
    C) one's hobbies and ideals  
    D) the environment and intelligence  

    正确答案： C



    Part III    Vocabulary and Structure  ( 10 minutes ) 



    Directions: There are a number of incomplete sentences in this part. For each sentence there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). Choose the ONE that best completes the sentence.


    41.
    	
    It means the ________ principles which members of the legal profession are expected to observe.
    A) ethical  
    B) ethics  
    C) ethnical  
    D) ethnic  

    正确答案： A
    42.
    	
    The royal couple has a 2-year-old daughter, born a year after the princess suffered a _________ .
    A) misunderstanding  
    B) misconception  
    C) mission  
    D) miscarriage  

    正确答案： D
    43.
    	
    To _________ any human technologically is against the basic dignity of the uniqueness of each human being.
    A) replicate  
    B) reproduce  
    C) reduce  
    D) regain  

    正确答案： A
    44.
    	
    With the clear perception of my ___________ , there fell upon me a blackness of despair.
    A) flight  
    B) delight  
    C) plight  
    D) light  

    正确答案： C
    45.
    	
    The United States corporations __________ to charity and other nonprofit purposes some $1,600 million annually.
    A) donate  
    B) donation  
    C) donor  
    D) dominate  

    正确答案： A
    46.
    	
    _________ and doubt lead to study and investigation, and investigation is the beginning of wisdom.
    A) Skeptical  
    B) Skeptic  
    C) Skepticism  
    D) Skeptics  

    正确答案： C
    47.
    	
    That ________ must be decided before any other questions can be dealt with.
    A) occasion  
    B) issue  
    C) question  
    D) theme  

    正确答案： B
    48.
    	
    Animal welfare did not become a ________ issue until the late 1970s.
    A) tremendous  
    B) condemning  
    C) argumentative  
    D) contentious  

    正确答案： D
    49.
    	
    The ________ of abuse in such a system is enormous.
    A) potential  
    B) potentials  
    C) odds  
    D) potency  

    正确答案： A
    50.
    	
    The divorce ________ rose from 20,000 in 1961 to 150,000 in 1985.
    A) ratio  
    B) percentage  
    C) rate  
    D) level  

    正确答案： C
    51.
    	
    A(n) _____ boat on the beach provided shelter for the travellers.
    A) exposed  
    B) immersed  
    C) upturned  
    D) multi-layered  

    正确答案： C
    52.
    	
    They managed to get the authentic painting by a famous ______ off the wall.
    A) donor  
    B) shipmate  
    C) surgeon  
    D) painter  

    正确答案： D
    53.
    	
    He wears knee and shoulder ______ and a helmet when he goes skateboarding.
    A) scars  
    B) pads  
    C) laces  
    D) joints  

    正确答案： B
    54.
    	
    We collected hundreds of _____ in support of not allowing cars into the city centre.
    A) signatures  
    B) awareness  
    C) stationery  
    D) statements  

    正确答案： A
    55.
    	
    His words were relayed into the crowded square by _____.
    A) veterinarian  
    B) loudspeaker  
    C) studio  
    D) toddler  

    正确答案： B
    56.
    	
    The mathematical concept of frames is utilized in the ________ of the properties of the sequence of sampling functions.
    A) analyst  
    B) analysis  
    C) analyses  
    D) analyze  

    正确答案： B
    57.
    	
    No one has ________ with information about the murder.
    A) come along  
    B) come across  
    C) come forward  
    D) come down  

    正确答案： C
    58.
    	
    He was quite ________ and was promoted almost at once.
    A) brilliant  
    B) tremendous  
    C) appropriate  
    D) prompt  

    正确答案： A
    59.
    	
    February normally has twenty-eight days, but every fourth year, ________ has twenty-nine.
    A) there  
    B) a leap year  
    C) which is a leap year  
    D) a leap year, it  

    正确答案： D
    60.
    	
    American public school curriculum is determined at the state or local level ________ the federal level.
    A) rather than  
    B) nor at the  
    C) is not determined  
    D) whereas  

    正确答案： A



    Part IV    Translation  ( 10 minutes ) 



    Directions: Translate the following sentences into English (with the given words or phrases).


    61. 	多利来到这个世界已经7年多了，但克隆人还是个颇具争议的话题。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： Dolly has been in this world for more than seven years, but human cloning is still a controversial topic.
    62. 	这次会议将聚焦在全球变暖问题上。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： This meeting will focus on the issue of global warming.
    63. 	世博会需要更多的志愿者来向人们提供帮助。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： The Expo needs more volunteers to come forward to help.
    64. 	这次事故是因为司机的疏忽而引起的。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： This accident resulted from the driver’s carelessness.
    65. 	从某种程度上来说，女生比男生在学习语言方面更有优势。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： In some ways, girls have more advantages than boys in terms of language learning.


