    全新版第二版综合B3U8-E

    Part I    Listening Comprehension  ( 16 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear ten statements. Numbers 1 to 6 are based on Text A while the rest are based on Text B. Each statement will be read ONLY ONCE. Listen carefully and decide whether each statement is true or false.


    1.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: It is absolutely wrong to put someone through what may well involve significant suffering for really no good end.

    正确答案： A
    2.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: As a pure scientist in some ways, the author knows that many different studies or findings could be used for evil.

    正确答案： A
    3.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: If the stem cell lines are created for any given individual and are later transplanted back into the individual, they will not be rejected by the individual.

    正确答案： A
    4.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: There are dialogues between the researchers in the embryonic stem cell field and those who oppose it.

    正确答案： B
    5.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: The author’s research got condemned by the Vatican and President Bush in the same week.

    正确答案： A
    6.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: That argument makes sense to the author to look at an embryo in a lab and give it all the rights of a human life.

    正确答案： B
    7.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: Just as was true of bans on abortion and on sex outside marriage, bans on human cloning are bound to be hard to enforce.

    正确答案： A
    8.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: A society that bans acts of human creation for no better reason than that their particular form defies nature and tradition is a society losing a significant part of its capacity to grow.

    正确答案： A
    9.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: One in a caste system is treated as fully human, but perhaps labeled untouchable.

    正确答案： B
    10.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: If human cloning is to be banned, the reasons had better be far more compelling than any thus far advanced.

    正确答案： A


    Section B 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear a passage three times. When the passage is read for the first time, you should listen carefully for its general idea. When the passage is read for the second time, you are required to fill in the blanks with the exact words you have just heard. Finally, when the passage is read for the third time, you should check what you have written.


            To Human Genome Project researchers, cloning refers to copying genes and other pieces of chromosomes to generate enough (11)_________________ material for further study. Two other types of cloning produce complete, (12)_________________ identical animals. Blastomere separation (sometimes called " (13)_________________ " after the naturally occurring process that creates identical twins) involves splitting a developing embryo soon after (14)_________________ of the egg by a sperm (sexual reproduction) to give rise to two or more embryos. The resulting (15)_________________ are identical twins (clones) containing DNA from both the mother and the father. Dolly, on the other hand, is the result of another type of cloning that produces an animal carrying the DNA of only one parent. Using somatic cell (16)_________________ transfer, scientists transferred genetic material from the nucleus of an (17)_________________ sheep’s udder cell to an egg whose nucleus, and thus its genetic material, had been removed. One goal of this is to develop efficient ways to alter animals genetically and (18)_________________ . Alterations have included adding genes (such as those for human proteins) to create drug-producing animals as well as inactivating genes to study the effects and possibly create animal models of human diseases. Cloning technology also may be used to raise animals having genetically altered organs suitable for transplanting to humans.
            The technique used to produce Dolly and other cloned animals is an extension of 40 years of research using DNA from nonhuman embryonic and fetal cells. Before this, scientists believed that once a cell became specialized the change was permanent and (19)_________________ in the cell became inactive. Dolly’s creators demonstrated that nuclei of an adult animal’s specialized cells can be made to revert to a non-specialized, embryonic state, thus (20)_________________ to give rise to any kind of cell.

    Script:         To Human Genome Project researchers, cloning refers to copying genes and other pieces of chromosomes to generate enough identical material for further study. Two other types of cloning produce complete, genetically identical animals. Blastomere separation (sometimes called “twinning” after the naturally occurring process that creates identical twins) involves splitting a developing embryo soon after fertilization of the egg by a sperm (sexual reproduction) to give rise to two or more embryos. The resulting organisms are identical twins (clones) containing DNA from both the mother and the father. Dolly, on the other hand, is the result of another type of cloning that produces an animal carrying the DNA of only one parent. Using somatic cell nuclear transfer, scientists transferred genetic material from the nucleus of an adult sheep’s udder cell to an egg whose nucleus, and thus its genetic material, had been removed. One goal of this is to develop efficient ways to alter animals genetically and reproduce them reliably. Alterations have included adding genes (such as those for human proteins) to create drug-producing animals as well as inactivating genes to study the effects and possibly create animal models of human diseases. Cloning technology also may be used to raise animals having genetically altered organs suitable for transplanting to humans.
            The technique used to produce Dolly and other cloned animals is an extension of 40 years of research using DNA from nonhuman embryonic and fetal cells. Before this, scientists believed that once a cell became specialized the change was permanent and other unneeded genes in the cell became inactive. Dolly’s creators demonstrated that nuclei of an adult animal’s specialized cells can be made to revert to a non-specialized, embryonic state, thus restoring the ability to give rise to any kind of cell.

    正确答案： identical

    正确答案： genetically

    正确答案： twinning

    正确答案： fertilization

    正确答案： organisms

    正确答案： nuclear

    正确答案： adult

    正确答案： reproduce them reliably

    正确答案： other unneeded genes

    正确答案： restoring the ability



    Part II    Reading Comprehension  ( 25 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, there is a passage with several blanks. You are required to select one word for each blank from a list of choices given in a word bank following the passage. Read the passage through carefully before making your choices. Each choice in the bank is identified by a letter. You may not use any of the words in the bank more than once.


            Human reproductive cloning is just simply wrong   21    from a medical standpoint and a scientific standpoint, even   22    any religious issues associated with it. The reason is that the majority of reproductive clones in other species are actually   23    , with very high   24    rates, very high stillbirth rates, fetal anomalies, death soon after birth, et cetera.
            It would just be absolutely wrong to take a human being and   25    what may well involve significant suffering for really no good end. Even though people could take the techniques that we’ve developed and   26    to do it, we hope that they would not.
            On the other hand,   27    cloning does not involve any type of risk to human life and actually provides   28    potential for the relief of suffering in real human beings who are going through some awful things.
            I’m a pure scientist in some ways, and I know that many different studies or findings could be used for   29    . Our job as scientists is to make the most of this technology and make it   30    to the greatest number of other scientists who can help us do good things with it.

    A) devil	B) tremendous	C) therapeutic	D) abnormal
    E) miscarriage	F) attempt	G) put them through	H) ethically
    I) ignoring	J) therapy	K) tempt	L) evil
    M) available	N) ethnics	O) get them through	

    21.	______________________

    正确答案： H

    22.	______________________

    正确答案： I

    23.	______________________

    正确答案： D

    24.	______________________

    正确答案： E

    25.	______________________

    正确答案： G

    26.	______________________

    正确答案： F

    27.	______________________

    正确答案： C

    28.	______________________

    正确答案： B

    29.	______________________

    正确答案： L

    30.	______________________

    正确答案： M


    Section B 

    Directions: There are several passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice.


    Passage One
    Questions 31 to 35 are based on the following passage.



            If a couple are infertile and wish they were not, that is sad. But there are treatments intended to deal with this sadness — known collectively as assisted reproductive technologies, or ARTs, which should be paid for out of public funds. Such funds are scarce, and infertility is not a life-threatening condition.
            However, two papers presented to the “State of the ART” conference held earlier this month in Lyon argue that in Europe, at least, there may be a public interest in promoting ARTs after all. The low fertility rate in many of that continent’s more developed countries means their populations are ageing and shrinking. If governments want to change this, ARTs — most significantly in-vitro fertilization (IVF) — could offer at least part of a way to do so.
            Tina Jensen of the University of Southern Denmark has just finished a study of more than 700,000 Danish women. She found that young women in Denmark have a significantly lower natural conception rate than in past decades. Whatever the cause, she also found that the effect has been almost completely compensated for by an increasing use of ARTs. Denmark’s native population is more or less stable, but some 3.9% of babies born there in 2003 were the result of IVF. The comparable figure for another northern European country, Britain, was 1.5%.
            Without IVF, then, the number of Danes would be shrinking fast. That may not have something to do with the fact that in Denmark the taxpayer will cover up to six cycles of IVF treatment. In Britain, by contrast, couples are supposed to be entitled to three cycles. In practice, many of the local trusts that dish the money out do not pay for any cycles at all. Jonathan Grant, the head of the Cambridge branch of the Rand Corporation, believes this is shortsighted.
            The cost of offering six cycles to couples would be an extra £250m-430m a year. That is not trivial, but Dr Grant reckons it is cheaper than other ways of boosting the birth rate.
            There are, of course, some disadvantages to promoting IVF. In particular, women who use it tend to be older than those who conceive naturally, and that can lead to congenital problems in their children. But if the countries of Europe do wish to keep their populations up, making IVF more widely available might be a good way of doing so.

    31.
    	
    According to the text, the public’s opinion on the infertility treatments is that _____.
    A) the treatments should be paid for out of public funds  
    B) the treatments are not so compulsory as they consume the limited public funds  
    C) the treatments are not necessarily only paid for out of public funds  
    D) the public is not obliged to pay for such treatments of no urgent nature  

    正确答案： B
    32.
    	
    According to the study conducted by Tina Jensen, which one of the following statements is true?
    A) ARTs have reversed the tendency of population decreasing in Denmark.  
    B) Danes’s problem of low natural conception has been completely counterbalanced by the widely use of ARTs.  
    C) The population of Denmark is not decreasing after the adoption of ARTs.  
    D) IVF has played an essential role in Denmark in terms of keeping up the number of population.  

    正确答案： D
    33.
    	
    From the paper of Dr Grant, it can be inferred that ______.
    A) the cost of offering six cycles of IVF to couples is not high at all  
    B) IVF treatment is an economical way of solving population shrinking  
    C) Britain does not promote adopting IVF to boost the birth rate  
    D) encouraging women to bear more babies by bonus is not so efficient to solve the problem of population shrinking  

    正确答案： B
    34.
    	
    The word “congenital” in the last paragraph most probably means _____.
    A) innate  
    B) instinctive  
    C) cerebral  
    D) acquired  

    正确答案： A
    35.
    	
    According to the passage, the author’s attitude towards promoting in-vitro fertilization can be said to be _____.
    A) supportive  
    B) opposing  
    C) ambiguous  
    D) objective  

    正确答案： A

    Passage Two
    Questions 36 to 40 are based on the following passage.

            The oldest and simplest method, then of describing differences in personality was to classify people according to types, and such a system is called a Typology.
            A famous example of this method was set forth in Greece about the year 400 BC. A physician named Hippocrates theorized that there were four fluids, or humors, in the body. Corresponding to each humor, he believed, there existed a definite type of personality.
            The four humors were blood, yellow bile, black bile, and phlegm. A person in whom all four humors were in perfect balance had a harmonious personality. If a person had too much blood, he was called sanguine (血红色), or cheerful and optimistic. Someone with too much yellow bile was choleric, or irritable and easily angered. Too much black bile made a person melancholy, or depressed and pessimistic. An oversupply of phlegm caused a human being to be phlegmatic, or slow and unfeeling. Scientists have long since discarded Hippocrates' fluid theory. But the names of the humors, corresponding to these temperaments, have survived and are still useful, to some extent, in describing personality.
            Other features of people, such as their faces and physics, have also been used to classify personality. Today, however, personality theories and classifications may also include factors such as heredity (遗传特征), the environment, intelligence, and emotional needs. Psychology, biology, and sociology are involved in these theories. Because of the complexity of human personality, present day theories are often very different from one another. Psychologists vary in their ideas about what is most important in determining personality.



    36.
    	
    According to Hippocrates' fluid theory, a man with too much phlegm will be ________.
    A) optimistic  
    B) easily angered  
    C) unexcitable  
    D) pessimistic  

    正确答案： C
    37.
    	
    The main idea of this passage is about ______.
    A) the complicated factors in determining one's personality  
    B) Hippocrates' fluid theory and its development  
    C) the past and today of personality classifications and theories  
    D) different personalities and their details  

    正确答案： C
    38.
    	
    At present, psychologists ___________.
    A) have common opinion about personality theories and classifications  
    B) use biology, archaeology and sociology to study personality theories  
    C) have abandoned Hippocrates' fluid theory entirely  
    D) all agree that human beings are characterized with complex personalities  

    正确答案： D
    39.
    	
    The third paragraph mainly talks about _________.
    A) Hippocrates' fluid theory  
    B) scientists' points of view on Hippocrates' fluid theory  
    C) Hippocrates' fluid theory and its fate  
    D) defects in Hippocrates' fluid theory  

    正确答案： C
    40.
    	
    According to this passage, the factors which are still NOT used to classify personality are ______.
    A) one's born features and needs of love and success  
    B) one's height and weight  
    C) one's hobbies and ideals  
    D) the environment and intelligence  

    正确答案： C



    Part III    Vocabulary and Structure  ( 9 minutes ) 



    Directions: There are a number of incomplete sentences in this part. For each sentence there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). Choose the ONE that best completes the sentence.


    41.
    	
    It will be particularly difficult to compensate for genes that malfunction during _________ development.
    A) fetal  
    B) fetus  
    C) embryo  
    D) baby  

    正确答案： A
    42.
    	
    To _________ any human technologically is against the basic dignity of the uniqueness of each human being.
    A) replicate  
    B) reproduce  
    C) reduce  
    D) regain  

    正确答案： A
    43.
    	
    With the clear perception of my ___________ , there fell upon me a blackness of despair.
    A) flight  
    B) delight  
    C) plight  
    D) light  

    正确答案： C
    44.
    	
    He can not find it in himself to ________ a mother who stole bread for a hungry child.
    A) flatter  
    B) sue  
    C) judge  
    D) condemn  

    正确答案： D
    45.
    	
    A Special Committee was also set up to consider the complex and ________ issues of compensation and betterment.
    A) easy  
    B) contentious  
    C) simple  
    D) consent  

    正确答案： B
    46.
    	
    Plastic bags are useful for holding many kinds of food, ___________ their clearness, toughness, and low cost.
    A) in deed  
    B) because  
    C) in spite of  
    D) by virtue of  

    正确答案： D
    47.
    	
    Their divorce ________ no communication.
    A) resulted from  
    B) resulted in  
    C) brought from  
    D) brought to  

    正确答案： A
    48.
    	
    In the old man’s opinion, that small cell phone costs ________ 100 yuan.
    A) no more than  
    B) not more than  
    C) nothing than  
    D) any than  

    正确答案： A
    49.
    	
    The fact that the plane was late added a further ________ to our journey.
    A) complication  
    B) complex  
    C) compliment  
    D) complicity  

    正确答案： A
    50.
    	
    He has done stupid things before, but to look for the escaping gas with a match really was the ________ silliness.
    A) triumphant  
    B) unanimous  
    C) ultimate  
    D) trivial  

    正确答案： C
    51.
    	
    These reforms will not ________ poverty and injustice.
    A) move  
    B) remove  
    C) decrease  
    D) degrade  

    正确答案： B
    52.
    	
    Each of us was reminded that we are here only for a time, and these counted days should be filled with things that last and matter: love for our families, love for our neighbors, and love for our country; _____ for life and to the giver of life.
    A) fancy  
    B) gratitude  
    C) reassurance  
    D) curiosity  

    正确答案： B
    53.
    	
    He had traveled far and alone; his whole life, indeed, had been a ______ path; for, with the lofty caution of his nature, he had kept himself apart from those who might otherwise have been his companions.
    A) swift  
    B) solitary  
    C) weary  
    D) considerate  

    正确答案： B
    54.
    	
    The streets became increasingly eerie in a fake ______ created by a smog of mist and smoke.
    A) lantern  
    B) twilight  
    C) stardust  
    D) reassurance  

    正确答案： B
    55.
    	
    Beauty is fine, but it doesn't do the laundry, buy groceries, cure measles, fill _____ tanks or keep our enemies at bay.
    A) frail  
    B) gas  
    C) cargo  
    D) icy  

    正确答案： B
    56.
    	
    "If they're flexible, we're flexible," the official was _____ as saying.
    A) commented  
    B) advertised  
    C) quoted  
    D) criticized  

    正确答案： C
    57.
    	
    Almost all the recent criticism from the mass media is ________ the ever increasing rate of unemployment.
    A) directed at  
    B) resulted from  
    C) resulted in  
    D) directed of  

    正确答案： A
    58.
    	
    The mathematical concept of frames is utilized in the ________ of the properties of the sequence of sampling functions.
    A) analyst  
    B) analysis  
    C) analyses  
    D) analyze  

    正确答案： B
    59.
    	
    Both the speaker and his speech were drowned out by the ________ of the crowd.
    A) approving  
    B) approval  
    C) disapproval  
    D) disapproving  

    正确答案： C
    60.
    	
    ________ and a mechanics instructor, interviewed at the air base, said that they were under orders not to fight.
    A) A flight instructor  
    B) There were an instructor  
    C) Because of the instructor  
    D) Because the instructor  

    正确答案： A



    Part IV    Translation  ( 10 minutes ) 



    Directions: Complete the sentences by translating into English the Chinese given in brackets.


    61. 	The boy was so much frightened ____________________ (他紧紧抓住母亲的手臂不肯松手).

    正确答案： that he caught tight his mother's arm and would not let loose
    62. 	____________________ (无论何时你想要表达你的意见), please look before leap.

    正确答案： Whenever you feel like expressing you opinion
    63. 	I think ____________________ (这一主题本应吸引哲学家们更多的注意力) than it has attracted attention from us.

    正确答案： this topic should have attracted far more attention from philosophers
    64. 	That day ____________________ (他有许多工作要做，忙得疲于奔命) and didn't have the least rest.

    正确答案： he was run off his feet with jobs to do
    65. 	Tom was born a cripple and ____________________ (申请过许多工作，都被拒绝) until he became a delivery boy for a Pizza Hut.

    正确答案： applied for numerous jobs only to be turned down


