    全新版第二版综合B3U8-D

    Part I    Listening Comprehension  ( 15 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear ten statements. Numbers 1 to 6 are based on Text A while the rest are based on Text B. Each statement will be read ONLY ONCE. Listen carefully and decide whether each statement is true or false.


    1.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: It is absolutely wrong to put someone through what may well involve significant suffering for really no good end.

    正确答案： A
    2.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: As a pure scientist in some ways, the author knows that many different studies or findings could be used for evil.

    正确答案： A
    3.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: If the stem cell lines are created for any given individual and are later transplanted back into the individual, they will not be rejected by the individual.

    正确答案： A
    4.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: There are dialogues between the researchers in the embryonic stem cell field and those who oppose it.

    正确答案： B
    5.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: The author’s research got condemned by the Vatican and President Bush in the same week.

    正确答案： A
    6.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: That argument makes sense to the author to look at an embryo in a lab and give it all the rights of a human life.

    正确答案： B
    7.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: Just as was true of bans on abortion and on sex outside marriage, bans on human cloning are bound to be hard to enforce.

    正确答案： A
    8.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: A society that bans acts of human creation for no better reason than that their particular form defies nature and tradition is a society losing a significant part of its capacity to grow.

    正确答案： A
    9.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: One in a caste system is treated as fully human, but perhaps labeled untouchable.

    正确答案： B
    10.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: If human cloning is to be banned, the reasons had better be far more compelling than any thus far advanced.

    正确答案： A


    Section B 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear a passage three times. When the passage is read for the first time, you should listen carefully for its general idea. When the passage is read for the second time, you are required to fill in the blanks with the exact words you have just heard. Finally, when the passage is read for the third time, you should check what you have written.


            To Human Genome Project researchers, cloning refers to copying genes and other pieces of chromosomes to generate enough (11)_________________ material for further study. Two other types of cloning produce complete, (12)_________________ identical animals. Blastomere separation (sometimes called " (13)_________________ " after the naturally occurring process that creates identical twins) involves splitting a developing embryo soon after (14)_________________ of the egg by a sperm (sexual reproduction) to give rise to two or more embryos. The resulting (15)_________________ are identical twins (clones) containing DNA from both the mother and the father. Dolly, on the other hand, is the result of another type of cloning that produces an animal carrying the DNA of only one parent. Using somatic cell (16)_________________ transfer, scientists transferred genetic material from the nucleus of an (17)_________________ sheep’s udder cell to an egg whose nucleus, and thus its genetic material, had been removed. One goal of this is to develop efficient ways to alter animals genetically and (18)_________________ . Alterations have included adding genes (such as those for human proteins) to create drug-producing animals as well as inactivating genes to study the effects and possibly create animal models of human diseases. Cloning technology also may be used to raise animals having genetically altered organs suitable for transplanting to humans.
            The technique used to produce Dolly and other cloned animals is an extension of 40 years of research using DNA from nonhuman embryonic and fetal cells. Before this, scientists believed that once a cell became specialized the change was permanent and (19)_________________ in the cell became inactive. Dolly’s creators demonstrated that nuclei of an adult animal’s specialized cells can be made to revert to a non-specialized, embryonic state, thus (20)_________________ to give rise to any kind of cell.

    Script:         To Human Genome Project researchers, cloning refers to copying genes and other pieces of chromosomes to generate enough identical material for further study. Two other types of cloning produce complete, genetically identical animals. Blastomere separation (sometimes called “twinning” after the naturally occurring process that creates identical twins) involves splitting a developing embryo soon after fertilization of the egg by a sperm (sexual reproduction) to give rise to two or more embryos. The resulting organisms are identical twins (clones) containing DNA from both the mother and the father. Dolly, on the other hand, is the result of another type of cloning that produces an animal carrying the DNA of only one parent. Using somatic cell nuclear transfer, scientists transferred genetic material from the nucleus of an adult sheep’s udder cell to an egg whose nucleus, and thus its genetic material, had been removed. One goal of this is to develop efficient ways to alter animals genetically and reproduce them reliably. Alterations have included adding genes (such as those for human proteins) to create drug-producing animals as well as inactivating genes to study the effects and possibly create animal models of human diseases. Cloning technology also may be used to raise animals having genetically altered organs suitable for transplanting to humans.
            The technique used to produce Dolly and other cloned animals is an extension of 40 years of research using DNA from nonhuman embryonic and fetal cells. Before this, scientists believed that once a cell became specialized the change was permanent and other unneeded genes in the cell became inactive. Dolly’s creators demonstrated that nuclei of an adult animal’s specialized cells can be made to revert to a non-specialized, embryonic state, thus restoring the ability to give rise to any kind of cell.

    正确答案： identical

    正确答案： genetically

    正确答案： twinning

    正确答案： fertilization

    正确答案： organisms

    正确答案： nuclear

    正确答案： adult

    正确答案： reproduce them reliably

    正确答案： other unneeded genes

    正确答案： restoring the ability



    Part II    Reading Comprehension  ( 25 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, there is a passage with several blanks. You are required to select one word for each blank from a list of choices given in a word bank following the passage. Read the passage through carefully before making your choices. Each choice in the bank is identified by a letter. You may not use any of the words in the bank more than once.


            Human reproductive cloning is just simply wrong   21    from a medical standpoint and a scientific standpoint, even   22    any religious issues associated with it. The reason is that the majority of reproductive clones in other species are actually   23    , with very high   24    rates, very high stillbirth rates, fetal anomalies, death soon after birth, et cetera.
            It would just be absolutely wrong to take a human being and   25    what may well involve significant suffering for really no good end. Even though people could take the techniques that we’ve developed and   26    to do it, we hope that they would not.
            On the other hand,   27    cloning does not involve any type of risk to human life and actually provides   28    potential for the relief of suffering in real human beings who are going through some awful things.
            I’m a pure scientist in some ways, and I know that many different studies or findings could be used for   29    . Our job as scientists is to make the most of this technology and make it   30    to the greatest number of other scientists who can help us do good things with it.

    A) devil	B) tremendous	C) therapeutic	D) abnormal
    E) miscarriage	F) attempt	G) put them through	H) ethically
    I) ignoring	J) therapy	K) tempt	L) evil
    M) available	N) ethnics	O) get them through	

    21.	______________________

    正确答案： H

    22.	______________________

    正确答案： I

    23.	______________________

    正确答案： D

    24.	______________________

    正确答案： E

    25.	______________________

    正确答案： G

    26.	______________________

    正确答案： F

    27.	______________________

    正确答案： C

    28.	______________________

    正确答案： B

    29.	______________________

    正确答案： L

    30.	______________________

    正确答案： M


    Section B 

    Directions: There are several passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice.


    Passage One
    Questions 31 to 35 are based on the following passage.



            Depending on whom you ask, the experiment announced at a Texas medical conference last week was a potential breakthrough for infertile women, a tragic failure or a dangerous step closer to the nightmare scenario of human cloning.
            Infertility was clearly the motivation when Chinese doctors used a new technique to help one of their countrywomen get pregnant. Using a technique developed by Dr. James Grifo at New York University, Dr. Zhuang Guanglun of Sun Yat-sen University in Guangzhou took the patient’s fertilized egg, scooped out the chromosome-bearing nuclear material and put it in a donated egg whose nucleus had been removed. In this more benign environment, development proceeded normally, and the woman became pregnant with triplets who carried a mix of her DNA and her husband’s — pretty much like any normal baby.
            What has made some doctors and ethicists upset is that this so-called nuclear-transfer technique has also been used to produce clones, starting with Dolly the sheep. The only significant difference is that with cloning, the inserted nucleus comes from a single, usually adult, cell, and the resulting offspring is genetically identical to the parent. Doing that with humans is ethically repugnant to many. Besides, for reasons that aren’t yet well understood, cloned animals often abort spontaneously or are born with defects; Dolly died very young, though she had seemed healthy. And because the Chinese woman’s twins were born prematurely and died, critics have suggested that cloning and nuclear transfer are equally risky for humans.
            Not likely, says Grifo. “The obstetric outcome was a disaster,” he admits, “but the embryos were chromosomally normal. We have no evidence that it had anything to do with the procedure.” Even so, concern over potential risks is why the Food and Drug Administration created a stringent approval process for such research in 2001 — a process that Grifo found so onerous that he stopped working on the technique and gave it to the researchers in China, where it was subsequently banned.
            The bottom line, say critics, is that perfecting a technique that could be used for human cloning, even if it were developed for another purpose, is just a bad idea — an assertion Zhuang rejects. “I agree that it makes sense to control these experiments,” he says. “But we’ve developed an effective technology to help people. We understand how to do it. We need it.”

    31.
    	
    What is implied in the first paragraph?
    A) Some people regard it as a tragic failure.  
    B) The new experiment means a breakthrough for some people.  
    C) People have different reactions to the new experiment.  
    D) The new experiment means a step further to the dangerous human cloning.  

    正确答案： C
    32.
    	
    The author uses the case of Dolly and the Chinese pregnant woman to show that _________.
    A) both nuclear-transfer and cloning are dangerous for humans and animals  
    B) both of them benefit from the new technique  
    C) both of them are the examples of technical failure  
    D) both of them are the fruits of the new technology  

    正确答案： A
    33.
    	
    Zhuang’s attitude toward the critics’ conclusion is one of __________.
    A) reserved consent  
    B) strong disapproval  
    C) slight contempt  
    D) enthusiastic support  

    正确答案： B
    34.
    	
    The only difference existing between nuclear-transfer and cloning technique is ________.
    A) whether it is used for research or for helping the infertile  
    B) whether the offspring looks like the parent  
    C) whether it is used in animals or human beings  
    D) whether the inserted nucleus comes from a single and usually adult cell  

    正确答案： D
    35.
    	
    The text intends to express the idea that _________.
    A) research of cloning has potential risks  
    B) the research of cloning should be stopped totally  
    C) ethics and research of cloning are in contradiction  
    D) researchers should have the right to continue the study of cloning  

    正确答案： C

    Passage Two
    Questions 36 to 40 are based on the following passage.

            The oldest and simplest method, then of describing differences in personality was to classify people according to types, and such a system is called a Typology.
            A famous example of this method was set forth in Greece about the year 400 BC. A physician named Hippocrates theorized that there were four fluids, or humors, in the body. Corresponding to each humor, he believed, there existed a definite type of personality.
            The four humors were blood, yellow bile, black bile, and phlegm. A person in whom all four humors were in perfect balance had a harmonious personality. If a person had too much blood, he was called sanguine (血红色), or cheerful and optimistic. Someone with too much yellow bile was choleric, or irritable and easily angered. Too much black bile made a person melancholy, or depressed and pessimistic. An oversupply of phlegm caused a human being to be phlegmatic, or slow and unfeeling. Scientists have long since discarded Hippocrates' fluid theory. But the names of the humors, corresponding to these temperaments, have survived and are still useful, to some extent, in describing personality.
            Other features of people, such as their faces and physics, have also been used to classify personality. Today, however, personality theories and classifications may also include factors such as heredity (遗传特征), the environment, intelligence, and emotional needs. Psychology, biology, and sociology are involved in these theories. Because of the complexity of human personality, present day theories are often very different from one another. Psychologists vary in their ideas about what is most important in determining personality.



    36.
    	
    According to Hippocrates' fluid theory, a man with too much phlegm will be ________.
    A) optimistic  
    B) easily angered  
    C) unexcitable  
    D) pessimistic  

    正确答案： C
    37.
    	
    The main idea of this passage is about ______.
    A) the complicated factors in determining one's personality  
    B) Hippocrates' fluid theory and its development  
    C) the past and today of personality classifications and theories  
    D) different personalities and their details  

    正确答案： C
    38.
    	
    At present, psychologists ___________.
    A) have common opinion about personality theories and classifications  
    B) use biology, archaeology and sociology to study personality theories  
    C) have abandoned Hippocrates' fluid theory entirely  
    D) all agree that human beings are characterized with complex personalities  

    正确答案： D
    39.
    	
    The third paragraph mainly talks about _________.
    A) Hippocrates' fluid theory  
    B) scientists' points of view on Hippocrates' fluid theory  
    C) Hippocrates' fluid theory and its fate  
    D) defects in Hippocrates' fluid theory  

    正确答案： C
    40.
    	
    According to this passage, the factors which are still NOT used to classify personality are ______.
    A) one's born features and needs of love and success  
    B) one's height and weight  
    C) one's hobbies and ideals  
    D) the environment and intelligence  

    正确答案： C



    Part III    Vocabulary and Structure  ( 10 minutes ) 



    Directions: There are a number of incomplete sentences in this part. For each sentence there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). Choose the ONE that best completes the sentence.


    41.
    	
    This announcement provoked a fierce and prolonged ___________ lasting from March until well into August.
    A) debating  
    B) debt  
    C) debate  
    D) probate  

    正确答案： C
    42.
    	
    It has been proved necessary to _________ against unequal treatment of women in employment.
    A) legislation  
    B) legal  
    C) legislate  
    D) legally  

    正确答案： C
    43.
    	
    _________ and doubt lead to study and investigation, and investigation is the beginning of wisdom.
    A) Skeptical  
    B) Skeptic  
    C) Skepticism  
    D) Skeptics  

    正确答案： C
    44.
    	
    A thorough __________ would take both the demand and supply into consideration.
    A) analyzing  
    B) analysis  
    C) analytical  
    D) analyze  

    正确答案： B
    45.
    	
    He can not find it in himself to ________ a mother who stole bread for a hungry child.
    A) flatter  
    B) sue  
    C) judge  
    D) condemn  

    正确答案： D
    46.
    	
    He learned that God only gives us a limited number of opportunities and that we must __________ them.
    A) make of  
    B) make up to  
    C) make over  
    D) make the most of  

    正确答案： D
    47.
    	
    Many of these “quick cures” are unproven, __________ marketed and useless or even dangerous.
    A) fraud  
    B) fraudulent  
    C) fraudulently  
    D) freak  

    正确答案： C
    48.
    	
    Her father reluctantly ________ to the marriage.
    A) consented  
    B) commented  
    C) contended  
    D) resented  

    正确答案： A
    49.
    	
    Their divorce ________ no communication.
    A) resulted from  
    B) resulted in  
    C) brought from  
    D) brought to  

    正确答案： A
    50.
    	
    The fact that the plane was late added a further ________ to our journey.
    A) complication  
    B) complex  
    C) compliment  
    D) complicity  

    正确答案： A
    51.
    	
    It does ________ to save money while you can.
    A) come to the sense  
    B) see sense  
    C) make sense  
    D) knock the sense  

    正确答案： C
    52.
    	
    The divorce ________ rose from 20,000 in 1961 to 150,000 in 1985.
    A) ratio  
    B) percentage  
    C) rate  
    D) level  

    正确答案： C
    53.
    	
    Joan rummaged (到处翻寻) in her drawer and came up with a(n) ______ of newspaper clippings (剪报).
    A) oven  
    B) kettle  
    C) fistful  
    D) carton  

    正确答案： C
    54.
    	
    He had traveled far and alone; his whole life, indeed, had been a ______ path; for, with the lofty caution of his nature, he had kept himself apart from those who might otherwise have been his companions.
    A) swift  
    B) solitary  
    C) weary  
    D) considerate  

    正确答案： B
    55.
    	
    "How clearly the events of that day ______ in my memory! I recall perfectly picking up the menu at the restaurant and seeing, instead of items of food, a bill which read like this."
    A) start out  
    B) kick out  
    C) stand out  
    D) go about  

    正确答案： C
    56.
    	
    Your left _____ hemisphere controls the right-hand side of your body.
    A) mechanical  
    B) humble  
    C) cerebral  
    D) theoretical  

    正确答案： C
    57.
    	
    His words were relayed into the crowded square by _____.
    A) veterinarian  
    B) loudspeaker  
    C) studio  
    D) toddler  

    正确答案： B
    58.
    	
    What is at ________ is whether she was responsible for her actions.
    A) problem  
    B) issue  
    C) discussion  
    D) reply  

    正确答案： B
    59.
    	
    The population of Houston was ravaged by yellow fever in 1839 ________ in 1867.
    A) it happened again  
    B) and again  
    C) was ravaged again  
    D) again once more  

    正确答案： B
    60.
    	
    According to Bernoulli's Principle, the higher the speed of a fluid gas, ________ the pressure.
    A) it will be lower  
    B) lower than the  
    C) the lower  
    D) lower it is  

    正确答案： C



    Part IV    Translation  ( 10 minutes ) 



    Directions: Translate the following sentences into English (with the given words or phrases).


    61. 	每年都有成千上万起信用卡欺骗案发生。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： Thousands of credit card frauds are committed every year.
    62. 	这次会议将聚焦在全球变暖问题上。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： This meeting will focus on the issue of global warming.
    63. 	世博会需要更多的志愿者来向人们提供帮助。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： The Expo needs more volunteers to come forward to help.
    64. 	有人向我们图书馆捐赠了5000多册图书。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： More than 5000 books were donated to our library.
    65. 	从某种程度上来说，女生比男生在学习语言方面更有优势。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： In some ways, girls have more advantages than boys in terms of language learning.


