    全新版第二版综合B3U8-F

    Part I    Listening Comprehension  ( 15 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear ten statements. Numbers 1 to 6 are based on Text A while the rest are based on Text B. Each statement will be read ONLY ONCE. Listen carefully and decide whether each statement is true or false.


    1.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: It is absolutely wrong to put someone through what may well involve significant suffering for really no good end.

    正确答案： A
    2.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: As a pure scientist in some ways, the author knows that many different studies or findings could be used for evil.

    正确答案： A
    3.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: If the stem cell lines are created for any given individual and are later transplanted back into the individual, they will not be rejected by the individual.

    正确答案： A
    4.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: There are dialogues between the researchers in the embryonic stem cell field and those who oppose it.

    正确答案： B
    5.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: The author’s research got condemned by the Vatican and President Bush in the same week.

    正确答案： A
    6.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: That argument makes sense to the author to look at an embryo in a lab and give it all the rights of a human life.

    正确答案： B
    7.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: Just as was true of bans on abortion and on sex outside marriage, bans on human cloning are bound to be hard to enforce.

    正确答案： A
    8.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: A society that bans acts of human creation for no better reason than that their particular form defies nature and tradition is a society losing a significant part of its capacity to grow.

    正确答案： A
    9.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: One in a caste system is treated as fully human, but perhaps labeled untouchable.

    正确答案： B
    10.
    	
    A) T  
    B) F  
    Script: If human cloning is to be banned, the reasons had better be far more compelling than any thus far advanced.

    正确答案： A


    Section B 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear a passage three times. When the passage is read for the first time, you should listen carefully for its general idea. When the passage is read for the second time, you are required to fill in the blanks with the exact words you have just heard. Finally, when the passage is read for the third time, you should check what you have written.


            Human cloning is no longer a dream in the wake of the birth of the first cloned sheep, Dolly, in 1996. Since that moment, not only the scientists in the field of (11)_________________ , but also the people over the whole world, have focused their (12)_________________ on whether humanity should be cloned or not. Undoubtedly, human cloning has already become the most (13)_________________ issue for a period. But seemingly, people haven’t got tired of the endless debates on this topic. The most (14)_________________ consideration during the debate is if human cloning can bring about good more than harm to society or not.
            Apparently, one of the well-known (15)_________________ brought about by human cloning is medical advance. Once a cell is (16)_________________ using the genetic materials derived from its host, the cell can act as a primary cell (17)_________________ of dividing and differentiating into specialized cells such as liver cells as well as nerve cells, and then develop into some kinds of vital organs. This sounds incredible, in particular to those who long for transplants to prolong their lives. Apart from this, during the process of nurturing the cloned embryo, scientists can extend their scope of knowledge about (18)_________________ and mechanism of certain fatal and incurable diseases like Parkinson’s disease, cancer and AIDs. On the basis of such discoveries, scientists are able to explore more ways to (19)_________________ . Furthermore, according to many scientists’ statements, the ageing process could be hindered if human cloning proceeded successfully. This means the impractical dream of extending the average lifespan of humanity to 120 years could (20)_________________ . As long as all nations strictly control the use of human cloning, human cloning will do more good than harm.

    Script:         Human cloning is no longer a dream in the wake of the birth of the first cloned sheep, Dolly, in 1996. Since that moment, not only the scientists in the field of biotechnology, but also the people over the whole world, have focused their attentions on whether humanity should be cloned or not. Undoubtedly, human cloning has already become the most controversial issue for a period. But seemingly, people haven’t got tired of the endless debates on this topic. The most crucial consideration during the debate is if human cloning can bring about good more than harm to society or not.
            Apparently, one of the well-known benefits brought about by human cloning is medical advance. Once a cell is duplicated using the genetic materials derived from its host, the cell can act as a primary cell capable of dividing and differentiating into specialized cells such as liver cells as well as nerve cells, and then develop into some kinds of vital organs. This sounds incredible, in particular to those who long for transplants to prolong their lives. Apart from this, during the process of nurturing the cloned embryo, scientists can extend their scope of knowledge about the mysterious causes and mechanism of certain fatal and incurable diseases like Parkinson’s disease, cancer and AIDs. On the basis of such discoveries, scientists are able to explore more ways to combat the diseases. Furthermore, according to many scientists’ statements, the ageing process could be hindered if human cloning proceeded successfully. This means the impractical dream of extending the average lifespan of humanity to 120 years could ultimately become reality. As long as all nations strictly control the use of human cloning, human cloning will do more good than harm.

    正确答案： biotechnology

    正确答案： attentions

    正确答案： controversial

    正确答案： crucial

    正确答案： benefits

    正确答案： duplicated

    正确答案： capable

    正确答案： the mysterious causes

    正确答案： combat the diseases

    正确答案： ultimately become reality



    Part II    Reading Comprehension  ( 25 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, there is a passage with several blanks. You are required to select one word for each blank from a list of choices given in a word bank following the passage. Read the passage through carefully before making your choices. Each choice in the bank is identified by a letter. You may not use any of the words in the bank more than once.


            I always thought that when our research was successful that I would just be pleased that we had   21    this when others had not. In reality, it is   22    — when you look through the microscope, you see what you may have looked like a long time ago, at least in part.
            When I looked down and saw that cloned   23    , it brought tears to my eyes. I had done this for my mother, and I realized,   24    she only been able to live a few years longer, maybe we could have used this technology to help her. It was   25    to see that potential, which she never had a chance to experience.
            There’s a big   26    out there that we decided to destroy these embryos for some reason. There was so much   27    about this process because of the scientific   28    from the past that it was critical that there be no doubt that they were clones.
            In the process of analysis, the embryos were destroyed by   29    . In other words, to get the   30    material from inside the cells to analyze it, you have to destroy the cell.

    A) if	B) genetically	C) fraud	D) transparent
    E) emotion	F) transcendent	G) blastocyst	H) skepticism
    I) emotional	J) skeptical	K) misconception	L) genetic
    M) had	N) necessity	O) accomplished	

    21.	______________________

    正确答案： O

    22.	______________________

    正确答案： F

    23.	______________________

    正确答案： G

    24.	______________________

    正确答案： M

    25.	______________________

    正确答案： I

    26.	______________________

    正确答案： K

    27.	______________________

    正确答案： H

    28.	______________________

    正确答案： C

    29.	______________________

    正确答案： N

    30.	______________________

    正确答案： L


    Section B 

    Directions: There are several passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice.


    Passage One
    Questions 31 to 35 are based on the following passage.



            Depending on whom you ask, the experiment announced at a Texas medical conference last week was a potential breakthrough for infertile women, a tragic failure or a dangerous step closer to the nightmare scenario of human cloning.
            Infertility was clearly the motivation when Chinese doctors used a new technique to help one of their countrywomen get pregnant. Using a technique developed by Dr. James Grifo at New York University, Dr. Zhuang Guanglun of Sun Yat-sen University in Guangzhou took the patient’s fertilized egg, scooped out the chromosome-bearing nuclear material and put it in a donated egg whose nucleus had been removed. In this more benign environment, development proceeded normally, and the woman became pregnant with triplets who carried a mix of her DNA and her husband’s — pretty much like any normal baby.
            What has made some doctors and ethicists upset is that this so-called nuclear-transfer technique has also been used to produce clones, starting with Dolly the sheep. The only significant difference is that with cloning, the inserted nucleus comes from a single, usually adult, cell, and the resulting offspring is genetically identical to the parent. Doing that with humans is ethically repugnant to many. Besides, for reasons that aren’t yet well understood, cloned animals often abort spontaneously or are born with defects; Dolly died very young, though she had seemed healthy. And because the Chinese woman’s twins were born prematurely and died, critics have suggested that cloning and nuclear transfer are equally risky for humans.
            Not likely, says Grifo. “The obstetric outcome was a disaster,” he admits, “but the embryos were chromosomally normal. We have no evidence that it had anything to do with the procedure.” Even so, concern over potential risks is why the Food and Drug Administration created a stringent approval process for such research in 2001 — a process that Grifo found so onerous that he stopped working on the technique and gave it to the researchers in China, where it was subsequently banned.
            The bottom line, say critics, is that perfecting a technique that could be used for human cloning, even if it were developed for another purpose, is just a bad idea — an assertion Zhuang rejects. “I agree that it makes sense to control these experiments,” he says. “But we’ve developed an effective technology to help people. We understand how to do it. We need it.”

    31.
    	
    What is implied in the first paragraph?
    A) Some people regard it as a tragic failure.  
    B) The new experiment means a breakthrough for some people.  
    C) People have different reactions to the new experiment.  
    D) The new experiment means a step further to the dangerous human cloning.  

    正确答案： C
    32.
    	
    The author uses the case of Dolly and the Chinese pregnant woman to show that _________.
    A) both nuclear-transfer and cloning are dangerous for humans and animals  
    B) both of them benefit from the new technique  
    C) both of them are the examples of technical failure  
    D) both of them are the fruits of the new technology  

    正确答案： A
    33.
    	
    Zhuang’s attitude toward the critics’ conclusion is one of __________.
    A) reserved consent  
    B) strong disapproval  
    C) slight contempt  
    D) enthusiastic support  

    正确答案： B
    34.
    	
    The only difference existing between nuclear-transfer and cloning technique is ________.
    A) whether it is used for research or for helping the infertile  
    B) whether the offspring looks like the parent  
    C) whether it is used in animals or human beings  
    D) whether the inserted nucleus comes from a single and usually adult cell  

    正确答案： D
    35.
    	
    The text intends to express the idea that _________.
    A) research of cloning has potential risks  
    B) the research of cloning should be stopped totally  
    C) ethics and research of cloning are in contradiction  
    D) researchers should have the right to continue the study of cloning  

    正确答案： C

    Passage Two
    Questions 36 to 40 are based on the following passage.

            The oldest and simplest method, then of describing differences in personality was to classify people according to types, and such a system is called a Typology.
            A famous example of this method was set forth in Greece about the year 400 BC. A physician named Hippocrates theorized that there were four fluids, or humors, in the body. Corresponding to each humor, he believed, there existed a definite type of personality.
            The four humors were blood, yellow bile, black bile, and phlegm. A person in whom all four humors were in perfect balance had a harmonious personality. If a person had too much blood, he was called sanguine (血红色), or cheerful and optimistic. Someone with too much yellow bile was choleric, or irritable and easily angered. Too much black bile made a person melancholy, or depressed and pessimistic. An oversupply of phlegm caused a human being to be phlegmatic, or slow and unfeeling. Scientists have long since discarded Hippocrates' fluid theory. But the names of the humors, corresponding to these temperaments, have survived and are still useful, to some extent, in describing personality.
            Other features of people, such as their faces and physics, have also been used to classify personality. Today, however, personality theories and classifications may also include factors such as heredity (遗传特征), the environment, intelligence, and emotional needs. Psychology, biology, and sociology are involved in these theories. Because of the complexity of human personality, present day theories are often very different from one another. Psychologists vary in their ideas about what is most important in determining personality.



    36.
    	
    According to Hippocrates' fluid theory, a man with too much phlegm will be ________.
    A) optimistic  
    B) easily angered  
    C) unexcitable  
    D) pessimistic  

    正确答案： C
    37.
    	
    The main idea of this passage is about ______.
    A) the complicated factors in determining one's personality  
    B) Hippocrates' fluid theory and its development  
    C) the past and today of personality classifications and theories  
    D) different personalities and their details  

    正确答案： C
    38.
    	
    At present, psychologists ___________.
    A) have common opinion about personality theories and classifications  
    B) use biology, archaeology and sociology to study personality theories  
    C) have abandoned Hippocrates' fluid theory entirely  
    D) all agree that human beings are characterized with complex personalities  

    正确答案： D
    39.
    	
    The third paragraph mainly talks about _________.
    A) Hippocrates' fluid theory  
    B) scientists' points of view on Hippocrates' fluid theory  
    C) Hippocrates' fluid theory and its fate  
    D) defects in Hippocrates' fluid theory  

    正确答案： C
    40.
    	
    According to this passage, the factors which are still NOT used to classify personality are ______.
    A) one's born features and needs of love and success  
    B) one's height and weight  
    C) one's hobbies and ideals  
    D) the environment and intelligence  

    正确答案： C



    Part III    Vocabulary and Structure  ( 10 minutes ) 



    Directions: There are a number of incomplete sentences in this part. For each sentence there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). Choose the ONE that best completes the sentence.


    41.
    	
    Doctors who attempt to ___________ human beings, Billings said, “should be treated as criminals.”
    A) cloned  
    B) clone  
    C) clones  
    D) cloning  

    正确答案： B
    42.
    	
    It means the ________ principles which members of the legal profession are expected to observe.
    A) ethical  
    B) ethics  
    C) ethnical  
    D) ethnic  

    正确答案： A
    43.
    	
    All he would say was that the cloned _________ was healthy and weighed roughly 6 pounds.
    A) fetus  
    B) child  
    C) baby  
    D) embryo  

    正确答案： A
    44.
    	
    Spaceships must attain __________ speeds to reach these planets in a reasonable time.
    A) tremendous  
    B) extreme  
    C) tremble  
    D) trending  

    正确答案： A
    45.
    	
    Plastic bags are useful for holding many kinds of food, ___________ their clearness, toughness, and low cost.
    A) in deed  
    B) because  
    C) in spite of  
    D) by virtue of  

    正确答案： D
    46.
    	
    Her father reluctantly ________ to the marriage.
    A) consented  
    B) commented  
    C) contended  
    D) resented  

    正确答案： A
    47.
    	
    We are working to change the popular ________ about AIDS.
    A) contempt  
    B) misconception  
    C) presentation  
    D) generalization  

    正确答案： B
    48.
    	
    ________, he never treated her as a servant.
    A) In a sense  
    B) Make a sense  
    C) To a sense  
    D) At a sense  

    正确答案： A
    49.
    	
    Surgeons have successfully ________ an artificial knee-joint.
    A) planted  
    B) implanted  
    C) fabricated  
    D) manufactured  

    正确答案： B
    50.
    	
    A survey is now being ________ nationwide.
    A) carried in  
    B) carried to  
    C) carried out  
    D) carried away  

    正确答案： C
    51.
    	
    Joan rummaged (到处翻寻) in her drawer and came up with a(n) ______ of newspaper clippings (剪报).
    A) oven  
    B) kettle  
    C) fistful  
    D) carton  

    正确答案： C
    52.
    	
    Several Asian governments welcomed the fall of Baghdad and made _____ of aid for post-war Iraq but the overall mood was one of cautious optimism.
    A) comments  
    B) delivery  
    C) pledges  
    D) joints  

    正确答案： C
    53.
    	
    I understand why I imagined being robbed by a man: they're physically more dominating and I've never _____ anyone being robbed by a female.
    A) heard of  
    B) been bound to  
    C) headed for  
    D) had second thoughts on  

    正确答案： A
    54.
    	
    The street lights come on at dusk and ______ at dawn.
    A) go off  
    B) take off  
    C) switch on  
    D) go about  

    正确答案： A
    55.
    	
    Beauty is fine, but it doesn't do the laundry, buy groceries, cure measles, fill _____ tanks or keep our enemies at bay.
    A) frail  
    B) gas  
    C) cargo  
    D) icy  

    正确答案： B
    56.
    	
    His style has been described variously as abrasive and ________, overbearing and pompous.
    A) quarrelsome  
    B) troublesome  
    C) respectable  
    D) contentious  

    正确答案： D
    57.
    	
    Almost all the recent criticism from the mass media is ________ the ever increasing rate of unemployment.
    A) directed at  
    B) resulted from  
    C) resulted in  
    D) directed of  

    正确答案： A
    58.
    	
    Both the speaker and his speech were drowned out by the ________ of the crowd.
    A) approving  
    B) approval  
    C) disapproval  
    D) disapproving  

    正确答案： C
    59.
    	
    The population of Houston was ravaged by yellow fever in 1839 ________ in 1867.
    A) it happened again  
    B) and again  
    C) was ravaged again  
    D) again once more  

    正确答案： B
    60.
    	
    Thunder occurs when an electrical charge passes through air, causing the heated air to expand and ________ layers of cooler air.
    A) collides violently with  
    B) violently colliding  
    C) collided with  
    D) collide violently with  

    正确答案： D



    Part IV    Translation  ( 10 minutes ) 



    Directions: Translate the following sentences into English (with the given words or phrases).


    61. 	每年都有成千上万起信用卡欺骗案发生。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： Thousands of credit card frauds are committed every year.
    62. 	大学生应该要充分利用在大学里的宝贵时间。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： College students should make the most of the precious time they have at college.
    63. 	世博会需要更多的志愿者来向人们提供帮助。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： The Expo needs more volunteers to come forward to help.
    64. 	这次事故是因为司机的疏忽而引起的。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： This accident resulted from the driver’s carelessness.
    65. 	这个歌星在开唱前总要检查一下是否一切都已就绪。

    ________________________________________

    正确答案： This singing star will always check whether everything is in place before he starts to sing.


