    全新版第二版听说B3U2-A

    Part I    Listening Comprehension  ( 29 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear several conversations. At the end of each conversation, one or more questions will be asked about what was said. Both the conversations and the questions will be spoken only once. After each question there will be a pause. During the pause, you must read the four choices marked A), B), C) and D), and decide which is the best answer.


    1.
    	
    A) A Father's Day card.  
    B) A Father's Day card and a new wallet.  
    C) Some family photos.  
    D) A card and a digital photo frame.  
    Script: Mary: Hi, Bob, have you decided on the gift to your father? Father's Day is just around the corner.
    Bob: I am still working on that! I need to buy a Father's Day card and I was thinking of buying him a new wallet. You see, his old one is broken. But yesterday I saw this lovely digital photo frame in the department store and I guess it'll make a better gift with our family photos on it.

    Question: What is Bob's decision on the Father's Day gift?
    
    正确答案： D
    2.
    	
    A) She will go with the man.  
    B) She will have a home-made lunch.  
    C) She will go for a snack.  
    D) She will have some canteen food.  
    Script: Man: What are you doing? Let's get into the hot lunch line.
    Woman: See this lunchbox? My mom made me brown-bag it today. She says that the lunches served at school aren't nutritious enough.

    Question: What will the woman have for lunch?
    
    正确答案： B
    3.
    	
    A) It is with brighter color and less noise.  
    B) It is with light weight and large screen.  
    C) It is with big screen and with better resolution.  
    D) It is with less noise and better picture.  
    Script: Man: This is what I'm talking about! It's time to upgrade to a big-screen TV and this is the perfect place to buy one.
    Woman: They certainly have a large selection. These new TVs have pictures that are much sharper than our current one.
    Man: There's no comparison. These new TVs have a much better resolution. Just look at the brightness and the contrast! Our old TV looks washed out by comparison.

    Question: What are the advantages of the new TV?
    
    正确答案： C
    4.
    	
    A) He is sad.  
    B) He is angry.  
    C) He is happy for the woman's decision.  
    D) He is concerned.  
    Script: Woman: Okay, I'm ready to walk my way to better fitness!
    Man: I'm glad you're so enthusiastic about starting to exercise.

    Question: What is the man's attitude towards the woman's statement?
    
    正确答案： C
    5.
    	
    A) The father is caring and busy.  
    B) She thinks the children are naughty.  
    C) She would like to help because the children are young.  
    D) She gives permission to the man's request because the children are good mannered.  
    Script: Man: Hi, Josephine, it's Ray. We have a meeting today at 10 a.m. and I was wondering if you would mind if I brought my kids with me. Their babysitter didn't show up.
    Woman: Oh, sure. That's no problem. Your children are so well behaved. Even at their age, they have perfect manners.

    Question: What is the woman's opinion on the man's request?
    
    正确答案： D
    Questions 6 to 8 are based on the conversation you have just heard.

    Script: Man: You look rather pale. Aren't you feeling well?
    Woman: Not very. I was sick most of the night. I didn't sleep very well.
    Man: What seems to be the matter? Is it the flu?
    Woman: No, I think it's something I ate. We ate at that new restaurant last night, and I must have eaten something that didn't agree with me.
    Man: Was it that new restaurant over on Fourth Street?
    Woman: As a matter of fact, it was. Why do you ask?
    Man: Because Jerry ate there last week and had the same kind of problem. He was sick the next day, too.
    Woman: That's interesting. Maybe the health authorities should investigate the place.
    Man: That's what I think. Two people with similar problems in such a short time can't just be coincidence!
    6.
    	
    A) She's got a flu.  
    B) She's got some food poisoning.  
    C) She's got a cold.  
    D) She's got a headache.  
    Script: What's wrong with the woman?
    
    正确答案： B
    7.
    	
    A) An old popular place they both went to.  
    B) A new restaurant over on Fourth Street.  
    C) A new restaurant over on Fifth Street.  
    D) An old restaurant over on Fifth Street.  
    Script: Which restaurant are they talking about?
    
    正确答案： B
    8.
    	
    A) He became a health authority.  
    B) He was dead.  
    C) He was sick for a year.  
    D) He had the same symptoms as the woman did.  
    Script: What happened to Jerry after eating in the restaurant?
    
    正确答案： D
    Questions 9 to 11 are based on the conversation you have just heard.

    Script: Man: Are you traveling on business?
    Woman: Yes, I am. I'm changing planes in Denver on my way to South Carolina, and then I'm off to Georgia on Wednesday. There's no rest for the weekend.
    Man: That's a lot of traveling. Doesn't your husband or boyfriend mind?
    Woman: Oh, I'm not married or seeing anyone. How about you? Where are you headed?
    Man: I'm going to Jacksonville, Florida to visit my parents for a few days, but I'll be back in Los Angeles by next weekend. Are you from L.A. originally?
    Woman: No, I was born and raised in Kentucky, but I've been living in L.A. for the past four years. What part of L.A. do you live in?
    Man: I live not too far from the airport in Westchester. Have you heard of it?
    Woman: That's a coincidence! I just rented an apartment in Westchester and I'm moving in when I get back. With all of this traveling, it made sense to move closer to the airport.
    Man: That seems like a wise move. You know, since I'm in the neighborhood, let me know if you need any help moving. I'd also be happy to show you around and give you a brief introduction of some of the better restaurants in the area. Here's my card. The number on the bottom is my cell phone.
    9.
    	
    A) Denver.  
    B) South Carolina.  
    C) Georgia.  
    D) Florida.  
    Script: Where will the woman be off to on Wednesday?
    
    正确答案： C
    10.
    	
    A) Tomorrow.  
    B) On Wednesday.  
    C) By next Saturday.  
    D) By next weekend.  
    Script: When will the man be back in L.A?
    
    正确答案： D
    11.
    	
    A) He wishes to establish a business relationship with her.  
    B) He hopes to visit her company when she is back.  
    C) He asks the woman to work for his company when she is back.  
    D) He would like to show the woman around the neighborhood.  
    Script: Why does the man present a card to the woman?
    
    正确答案： D


    Section B 

    Direstions：Listen to three short passages. At the end of each passage, you will hear some questions. All the recordings will be played once only. After you hear a question, please choose the best answer from the four choices marked A), B), C) and D).


    Passage One
    Questions 12 to 14 are based on the passage you have just heard.

    Script:         Morgan Robertson, in 1898, wrote Futility. It described the maiden voyage of a transatlantic luxury liner named the Titan. Although it was praised as being unsinkable, it strikes an iceberg and sinks with much loss of life. In 1912 the Titanic, a transatlantic luxury liner widely praised as unsinkable struck an iceberg and sank with great loss of life on her maiden voyage. In the book, the Month of the Wreck was April, same as in the real event. There were 3,000 passengers on the book; in reality, 2,207. In the book, there were 24 lifeboats; in reality, 20.
            Months after the Titanic sank, a tramp steamer was traveling through the foggy Atlantic with only a young boy on watch. It came into his head that it had been thereabouts that the Titanic had sunk, and he was suddenly terrified by the thought of the name of his ship ― the Titanian. Panic-stricken, he sounded the warning. The ship stopped, just in time: a huge iceberg loomed out of the fog directly in their path. The Titanian was saved.
    12.
    	
    A) The name of a Greek God.  
    B) The name of a novel by Morgan Robertson.  
    C) The name of an oil liner.  
    D) The name of a luxury liner.  
    Script: What was the Titanic in reality?
    
    正确答案： D
    13.
    	
    A) 3,000.  
    B) 24.  
    C) 2,207.  
    D) 20.  
    Script: How many lifeboats were there as the book described?
    
    正确答案： B
    14.
    	
    A) The boy on watch saved the ship by stopping it in time before it struck a huge iceberg.  
    B) The ship was lost in the fog.  
    C) The boy was a reader of the book and decided to change the name of his ship.  
    D) The boy was terrified and forgot to sound the warning.  
    Script: What happened to the tramp steamer named Titanian?
    
    正确答案： A

    Passage Two
    Questions 15 to 17 are based on the passage you have just heard.

    Script:         A falling baby, saved two times by the same man. Twin brothers, killed along the same road, two hours apart. The world is filled with astonishing occurrences of coincidence that defy explanation. Are these incredible true stories of mere coincidence ... or the hand of fate?
            In September 1955, James Dean was killed in a horrific car accident whilst he was driving his Porsche sports car. After the crash the car was seen as very unlucky.
            When the car was pulled away from the accident scene and taken to a garage, the engine slipped out and fell onto a mechanic, shattering both of his legs.
            Eventually the engine was bought by a doctor, who put it into his racing car and was killed shortly afterwards, during a race. Another racing driver, in the same race, was killed in his car, which had a part of James Dean's car fitted to it.
            When James Dean's Porsche was later repaired, the garage it was in was destroyed by fire.
            Later the car was displayed in Sacramento, but it fell off its mount and broke a teenager's hip.
            In Oregon, the trailer that the car was mounted on slipped from its towbar and smashed through the front of a shop.
            Finally, in 1959, the car mysteriously broke into 11 pieces while it was sitting on steel supports.
    15.
    	
    A) The car was broken and given up by the family.  
    B) The car was regarded as unlucky.  
    C) The car was sold to another person.  
    D) The car was broken into 11 pieces.  
    Script: What happened to the Porsche sports car after the car accident in September 1955?
    
    正确答案： B
    16.
    	
    A) The garage was sold to a foreigner.  
    B) The garage became a storehouse.  
    C) The garage was destroyed by a fire.  
    D) The garage was repaired as well.  
    Script: When James Dean's Porsche was later repaired, what happened to the garage it was in?
    
    正确答案： C
    17.
    	
    A) In 1955.  
    B) In 1957.  
    C) In 1958.  
    D) In 1959.  
    Script: When did the car finally break up into pieces?
    
    正确答案： D

    Passage Three
    Questions 18 to 20 are based on the passage you have just heard.

    Script:         A WESTWOOD youngster was delighted to be reunited with his stolen toy car after his big brother spotted it while on a trip to the police station.
            Three-year-old Fergus Mackenzie was heartbroken to find his favorite toy ― a yellow go-kart type car ― had been stolen from his grandparents back garden in St Leonards.
            The youngster looked forward to the regular trips to their house as it meant he could get out and about in the toy car, but last week when he arrived it was nowhere to be seen.
            However, by strange coincidence his older brother Finn went on a tour of the police station a few days later with the Cubs and spotted the missing toy car in their lost property room.
            As a result, Fergus was reunited with the toy, which had been handed into the police by a kind soul who had found it on St Leonards Road.
            The boys' mom Kirsten told the News: "We are so grateful someone handed it into the police.
            "I was surprised anyone had done so ― the toy is a bit shabby as it originally belonged to Finn when he was a toddler and he is now 10-years-old."
            "When Fergus gets to his gran and papa's the first thing he does is look for it and he was so sad when it was gone. He was really excited when he got it back as we all thought it was gone forever."
            "We'd like to thank the kind person who handed it in."
            Sergeant Stuart Cluckie of East Kilbride Police added: "People aren't aware of the distress their actions can cause in situations like this."
            "However, we are always happy when we can reunite a youngster with his favorite toy."
    18.
    	
    A) Fergus Mackenzie's.  
    B) Finn Mackenzie's.  
    C) St Leonards'.  
    D) Kristen Mackenzie's.  
    Script: Whose toy car was it?
    
    正确答案： A
    19.
    	
    A) Because she thought the toy was gone forever.  
    B) Because the toy was shabby and it was very old.  
    C) Because the son didn't like the toy.  
    D) Because the family had bought a new toy car for the boy.  
    Script: Why did the mother feel surprised when the toy was found?
    
    正确答案： B
    20.
    	
    A) Three.  
    B) Four.  
    C) Six.  
    D) Ten.  
    Script: How old was the elder brother now?
    
    正确答案： D


    Section C 

    Directions: In this section, you will hear a passage three times. When the passage is read for the first time, you should listen carefully for its general idea. When the passage is read for the second time, you are required to fill in the blanks with the exact words you have just heard. Finally, when the passage is read for the third time, you should check what you have written.


            At some time or another it happens to all of us. There's that certain number that pops up wherever you go. Hotel rooms, airline (21)_________________ , street addresses ― its haunting presence cannot be escaped. Or, you're in your car, (22)_________________ humming a song. You turn on the radio. A sudden chill prickles your spine. That same song is now (23)_________________ from the speaker.
            Coincidence, you tell yourself. Or is it?
            For most (24)_________________ scientists, experiences like this, however strange and recurrent, are nothing but lawful (25)_________________ of chance, a creation ― not of the divine or mystical ― but of simply that which is possible. (26)_________________ of natural law, they argue, causes us to fall (27)_________________ to superstitious thinking, inventing supernatural causes where none exist. In fact, say these statistical law-abiding rationalists, the (28)_________________ manifestation of the rare and improbable in daily life is not only permissible, but inevitable.
            Consider this: from a well-shuffled deck of fifty-two playing cards, the mathematical odds of dealing a hand of thirteen (29)_________________ cards are about 635,000,000,000 to one. (This means that, in dealing the hand, there exist as many as 635,000,000,000 different hands that may possibly appear.) What statisticians tell us, though, is that these billions of hands are all equally likely to occur, and that one of them is absolutely certain to occur each time the hand is dealt. Thus, any hand that is dealt, including the most rare and improbable hand is, in terms of probability, merely one of a number of equally likely events, one of which was (30)_________________ to happen.

    Script:         At some time or another it happens to all of us. There's that certain number that pops up wherever you go. Hotel rooms, airline terminals, street addresses ― its haunting presence cannot be escaped. Or, you're in your car, absently humming a song. You turn on the radio. A sudden chill prickles your spine. That same song is now pouring from the speaker.
            Coincidence, you tell yourself. Or is it?
            For most mainstream scientists, experiences like this, however strange and recurrent, are nothing but lawful expressions of chance, a creation ― not of the divine or mystical ― but of simply that which is possible. Ignorance of natural law, they argue, causes us to fall prey to superstitious thinking, inventing supernatural causes where none exist. In fact, say these statistical law-abiding rationalists, the occasional manifestation of the rare and improbable in daily life is not only permissible, but inevitable.
            Consider this: from a well-shuffled deck of fifty-two playing cards, the mathematical odds of dealing a hand of thirteen specified cards are about 635,000,000,000 to one. (This means that, in dealing the hand, there exist as many as 635,000,000,000 different hands that may possibly appear.) What statisticians tell us, though, is that these billions of hands are all equally likely to occur, and that one of them is absolutely certain to occur each time the hand is dealt. Thus, any hand that is dealt, including the most rare and improbable hand is, in terms of probability, merely one of a number of equally likely events, one of which was bound to happen.
    
    正确答案： terminals
    
    正确答案： absently
    
    正确答案： pouring
    
    正确答案： mainstream
    
    正确答案： expressions
    
    正确答案： Ignorance
    
    正确答案： prey
    
    正确答案： occasional
    
    正确答案： specified
    
    正确答案： bound



    Part II    Oral Tasks  ( 2 minutes ) 



    Section A 

    Directions: Interpret the following Chinese passage into English. You can either interpret it sentence by sentence or give out the main points in your own words. You will have TWO minutes for preparation and THREE minutes for interpretation.
    31.	        成功是偶然的吗？没有人能不努力就成功。托马斯•爱迪生成功了，那是因为他试验了上千次才找到最好的灯丝材料。所有的成功都需要努力的工作。如果你想成功，首先努力工作，然后才是偶然的运气。

    思考/准备


    Section B 

    Directions: Describe, comment or elaborate on the following pictures, phenomenon, event or epigram. You will have TWO minutes for preparation and THREE minutes for presentation.
    32.	Coincidences are familiar to all of us. They can involve startling conjunctions of events, such as chance meetings with old friends, or coincidences of personal habits or of anniversaries. Should we be surprised by coincidences? Do you believe in coincidence? Do you have any story of coincidence?

    思考/准备


